<translations>
  <!-- Header -->
  <translation key="header-welcome">
    <value>Hi 👋</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="header-desc">
    <value>I'm Av32000, frontend and backend developer, passionate about IT
      and new technologies!</value>
  </translation>
  <!-- Story -->
  <translation key="story-title">
    <value>My Story</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="story-1">
    <value>I started programming at the age of <span class="accent">10 yo</span> coding small
      website in HTML and CSS.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="story-2">
    <value>I then put aside these languages in favor of <span class="accent">C#</span> through which
      I discovered the <span class="accent">basics</span> of object-oriented programming. With .NET,
      I created my firsts <span class="accent">Windows</span> applications then with Unity, smalls <span
        class="accent">video games</span>.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="story-3">
    <value>At 14, I started using <span class="accent"> Discord</span> massively and interested in
      their API. This is how I discovered <span class="accent"> JavaScript</span> and <span
        class="accent">Node.JS</span> and fell in <span class="accent">love</span> with it.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="story-4">
    <value>In this way, I discovered the world of the <span class="accent">backend</span> and <span
        class="accent">APIs</span> and I immediately understood that I wanted to make it my <span
        class="accent">futur jobs</span>.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="story-5">
    <value>Today, I try to discover as many new technologies as possible. Like <span class="accent">
      React</span> and <span class="accent">Docker</span> to broaden my range of skills.</value>
  </translation>
  <!-- Skills -->
  <translation key="skills-title">
    <value>My Skills</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="git-1">
    <value>I've been a big Git user for a long time. I immediately liked the way it worked, which
      makes it so complex and powerful.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="git-2">
    <value>I use it in every project I start, whether for its ease of versioning an application or
      for its ability to instantly synchronize code between multiple devices.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="git-3">
    <value>I've read and watched a lot of books and tutorials to get to know it inside out, and even
      if I'm not an expert, I know most of the important functions very well.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="node-1">
    <value>I discovered Node.JS on Discord when I wanted to learn how to code bots.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="node-2">
    <value>I quickly fell in love with this framework and now use it in almost all my projects,
      whether with libraries such as express.js for APIs, react for web and electron for software.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="node-3">
    <value>This framework allowed me to discover my great passion for the backend with Javascript.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="js-1">
    <value>I discovered JavaScript when I got interested in the Discord API. It was a revelation for
      me. I immediately became a fan of this language, both for its strange simplicity and for the
      way it works for everything (web, servers, software...).</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="js-2">
    <value>As I'm not a big fan of design, Javascript lets me simply code applications that run in a
      terminal (with Node), so I don't have to create a UI.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="react">
    <value>I really like React for its ease of use. I've used it in many projects, and
      if at first I didn't understand the interest, I now use it very (sometimes too) often.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="docker-1">
    <value>I haven't used Docker much for lack of cases where I really need it. But having quickly
      realized the value of knowing how to use it in company, I forced myself to learn even the
      basics.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="docker-2">
    <value>Although I'm far from being a pro, I know how it works and how to use it in the simplest
      cases.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="cs-1">
    <value>C# was the first real programming language I learned. It introduced me to all the doors
      that programming can open, and that's why it's so important to me.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="cs-2">
    <value>I coded my first Windows applications with it, and although I prefer JavaScript today, I
      still often use it in many projects.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="unity">
    <value>Unity allowed me to discover much more advanced programming concepts, and was a big plus
      in my learning curve. Even though I've never done any major projects with it, it has helped me
      improve in a number of areas.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="java-1">
    <value>I discovered Java while creating mods and plugins for the Minecraft game. I've also used
      it in small Android application projects. Even if I rarely use it, I've used it enough to have
      a good overall knowledge of it.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="java-2">
    <value>Even so, I still find it hard to know when to use it where JavaScript is better on almost
      every subject.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="jest-1">
    <value>I've heard about Jest for a very long time without really understanding the interest.
      This recently that I started using it and realized what I'd been missing all along.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="jest-2">
    <value>Having only been using it for a few months, I'm not yet familiar with all its functions
      and use cases, but it saves me so much time in so many situations that I'm looking to learn
      more and more.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="github-1">
    <value>For me, GitHub is an essential for almost every IT project. Whether it's for code
      storage, collaboration, actions, issues, pull requests and so on. I use it every
      day in all my projects and I'm always very happy with it.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="github-2">
    <value>It took me a while to learn how to use it perfectly, but for me it's the best investment
      of time I've ever made. I put all my projects on it and I wouldn't change it for any
      alternative. </value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="html-1">
    <value>I have a special relationship with HTML because it was the first programming language I
      ever worked with. It's what got me into the exciting world of computing.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="html-2">
    <value>I don't have much more to say about it, given its simplicity.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="css-1">
    <value>To be honest, when I first discovered CSS, I hated it! I found it too complex and I
      couldn't get anything good out of it. So I put it to one side and filed it away as a language
      I wouldn't touch again.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="css-2">
    <value>A few years later, I tried using it again and, with the experience I'd gained in the
      meantime, it seemed much simpler than I remembered. Paradoxically, it's now my favourite
      design method, given the
      astronomical amount of possibilities it offers.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="css-3">
    <value>With time, I think I've mastered it quite now.</value>
  </translation>
  <!-- Projects -->
  <translation key="projects-title">
    <value>My Projects</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="discord-badge">
    <value>Discord Badge is a Discord Bot that uses its API to retrieve a badge indicating your
      Discord status (Online, Offline...). It's very easy to use, and can be used on a website or
      GitHub profile, for example.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="code-lyoko-uhc">
    <value>Code Lyoko UHC is a UHC Minecraft plugin based on the Code Lyoko universe. Each player is
      assigned a role corresponding to a character from the series, and must, alone or with allies,
      eliminate all other players to win the game. Each role has its own powers and characteristics,
      creating a wide range of possible strategies.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="gartic-cheat">
    <value>Gartic Cheat is a C#-coded program that lets you draw for yourself in the Gartic Phone
      game. Simply import an image, select a drawing area and let the program take control of your
      mouse to draw for you.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="parthenis">
    <value>Parthénis is an artificial intelligence playing the game 2048. For each move, it
      calculates the score and the number of empty squares. It also has a depth system that enables
      it to predict several moves in advance.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="youtube-downloader">
    <value>Youtube Downloader is an easy-to-use webapp that lets you download Youtube videos quickly
      and free of charge. It uses the express.js and YouTube.js libraries.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="embed-builder">
    <value>Embed Builder is a Discord Bot that lets you create and send a fully customizable embed
      with a simple command. It's very easy to use, yet very complete, offering full embed
      customization.</value>
  </translation>
  <translation key="clyde-gateway">
    <value>Clyde Gateway is a simple, lightweight library for connecting your bot to the Discord
      gateway. It allows your bot to listen to all events and react to them in real time. It also
      lets you change your bot's status (Online, Idle...) and activity (Playing at...).</value>
  </translation>
  <!-- Other -->

</translations>